The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
A disciple of the Heavenly Fate Sect ?
What are you doing here ?
They have both new and old wounds.
They must have been caused by the demonic beasts.
Greed and the others have been trapped here for over 100 years.
With his strength,
even if he were trapped here,
he wouldn't have allowed the others to be injured to this extent.
This looks like an internal conflict.
Senior Brother asked you a question !
How dare you stay silent !?
The 12 Sword are led by Chen Long.
I still need to test Chen Long's attitude.
Disperse.
You...
My sword !
How dare you !?
You Heavenly Fate Thief !
He stole the sword and erased its spirit...
How vicious !
Scumbag !
I will tear you to pieces !
My Junior Brother was reckless, ignorant,
and has offended fellow cultivator.
I hope you can forgive him.
Senior Brother,
you...
And this sword ?
My Junior Brother was rude,
this sword now belongs to fellow cultivator.
Consider it an apology.
Since that's the case,
I will let bygones be bygones.
Little brat,
since your friend is here,
why isn't he showing himself ?
My friend is introverted
and doesn't like crowds.
How is Senior called ?
Brother Wang,
Senior's Daoist name is Greed.
He is of the same generation as our masters.
This place
was originally a cultivation site found for us by Senior.
I don't know why,
but the only exit has been blocked by a pack of demonic beasts.
If those beasts hadn't heavily injured Senior,
limiting his cultivation to Peak Late stage Ascendant,
we wouldn't have been trapped here for 100 years.
This Chen Long is smart.
A few seemingly casual words
have already painted the whole situation.
When our Divine Senses clashed before,
he didn't seem heavily injured.
Judging from Chen Long's tone,
he seems unaware of the token.
Greed is feigning weakness
to stay lurking here for 100 years.
He must be waiting for something.
What's going to happen ?
It must be something related to the token.
If I want to learn his plan,
I must break the stalemate
and force him to act.
Fellow cultivator Chen Long,
in front of this crisis,
why don't we set aside our sect's grudges
to escape together ?
Senior Greed,
with the help of fellow cultivator Wang,
I'm sure that we can
break out of here safely.
Since Senior is injured,
you shouldn't overexert yourself.
My friend and I are willing to do the hard work.
It doesn't matter if your cultivation
is only Ascendant.
If this old man refuses again,
I'm afraid you will suspect I am hiding something.
Fine.
I will lead you in breaking through that pack of beasts.
Almost there...
It's happening soon...
I see !
That's why the Mosquito Beast was attracted earlier.
The Mosquito Beasts are surrounding this place...
because of Greed !
If Greed only plotted for the token,
he could have acted alone.
He wouldn't have needed the Da Lou Sword Sect disciples.
Unless...
he has another use for them.
Greed,
what are you doing !?
The purple mist will finally become one again !
I, Greed,
will sacrifice you all to fulfill my wish !
What !?
Let's welcome the token of the tide !
The edge of this purple mist
is impossible to break
with my Ascendant cultivation.
The formation is reinforced with celestial spiritual energy.
Unless one has a Celestial Root,
they can't leave.
Fortunately, I am a Celestial Sword Spirit.
This formation has no effect on me.
Quick, I will carry you out !
Wait a moment, Senior.
I can manage for now.
Since things have come to this,
there's no rush to break out.
The real show is finally starting !
This thing is getting stronger and stronger !
We...We can't stop it !
Senior Brother,
the sword energy Master gave you is stronger than ours.
It might be able help us escape this formation !
Master's sword energy is limited.
I'm not confident in taking all of you out.
Junior Brothers,
I'm sorry !
What a deep "brotherly love"...
Senior Brothers,
let's take back the swords he stole !
We might be able to escape with a sword formation !
Since you attacked first,
don't blame me for being ruthless.
Senior,
give me 10 more breaths.
Just 10 breaths then.
After that, I'm taking you out of there.
Alright.
Ten...
Seven...
Five...
Let's die together !
Three...
Two...
One !
It's a pity that
I couldn't get all of them.
Your attempt to snatch food from the tiger's mouth
is the most audacious thing I've ever seen.
The token is about to take shape !
I can't miss this opportunity !
What do you intend to do ?
The Juniors of the Da Lou Sword Sect
shall now feed these beasts !
Seven Magic Needles,
imprint !
Seven Magic Needles
Incompetent...
Imprint again !
A King Beast Inheritance !
Unless Greed dies,
neither of us will make it out alive.
What do you think ?
Let's join forces.
We'll kill this old fox together !
If I need to fight these beasts,
I will die for sure.
Greed's\NDeath Devourer, first form
Death Devourer, first form !
Death Devourer, second form !
Greed's\NDeath Devourer, second form
Extract...
the mountain's soul !
My cultivation indeed can't compare with Ling Tianhou's or the All-Seer's.
But this old man's spells
aren't things I learned from others !
What kind of spell is this !?
The mountain's soul actually contains celestial spiritual energy...
This celestial spiritual energy doesn't come from Greed,
it comes from the mountain's soul itself.
Little brats,
this mountain is from the Celestial Realm !
I pulled it out tens of thousands of years ago !
What do you plan to do ?
Force them to fight each other.
Greed sacrificed my Junior Brothers to condense this thing.
If both of them care so much about it,
it must be a rare treasure !
Even if I need to use all of Master's sword energy,
I must obtain it !
Junior, how dare you !
Celestial artifact, Heaven Confusion Incense.
Heaven Confusion Incense
Even a Celestial would be entranced by it !
Since you forced me to use this artifact,
I will definitely tear you to pieces !
How can this be !?
The token
is mine for the taking !
Stop !
You little bastard !
You won't get away !
He must still have a trump card.
Senior,
faster !
Every time Greed does something,
he pulls out an incredible celestial artifact.
If he found all of them,
then he really is blessed by the heavens.
Ancient God Tu Si's furnace !
Spatial Reversal,
reverse the heavens and the earth !
Greed's\NSpatial Reversal
I must survive !
So what if you have an expert protecting you ?
Once you're in my grasp,
you're as good as dead !
Mountain and River Painting,
open !
Greed's\NMountain and River Painting
What a powerful artifact !
You will...
Disperse for me !
Wang Lin,
leave quickly !
Where do you think you're going ?
I'm your opponent !
Second Origin Soul !
Kill him !
He
will die for sure.
Greed has too many artifacts.
Even if Senior Zhou Yi wins,
it will take time.
What kind of entity is his second Origin Soul made of
to be this powerful ?
Greed controls his Second Origin Soul with this seal.
In that case...
How is this possible !?
The seal is shattered.
His second Origin Soul should be weakened now.
What !?
Ancient Thunder Dragon\NGreed's Second Origin Soul
Greed...
This person really is full of treasures,
even his second Origin Soul is made of an Ancient Thunder Dragon.
Destroying the seal
has released it.
The Thunder Dragon is aggressive
and I'm no match for it.
But no matter the danger,
I, Wang Lin,
must fight for a slim chance of survival !
The square-shaped furnace Greed pulled out is the exact same furnace we saw Tu Si craft when Wang Lin obtains the Ancient God memory inheritance in episode 36 which is why he instantly recognizes it.\N\N\N“Greed… Greed… This person really is full of treasures, even his second Origin Soul is a dragon! The furnace that Tu Si refined back then also landed in his hands… His cultivation level is also high, so he can be considered someone who has the heavens’ own luck!”\N\NWang Lin bitterly smiled. He didn’t know that back when Greed was only eight and hadn’t even started cultivating, he found a five-hundred-year-old Soloman’s Seal (plant) while playing. He took it home and ate it after breaking it. Not only was he not killed by the surge of energy inside it, but it laid his foundation as a cultivator.\N\N\NFun Fact if you read I Shall Seal the Heavens (Renegade Immortal's sequel), Meng Hao uses a very very similar artifact. Lore-wise they are not the same item, but their similarity makes me think Meng Hao's Lightning Cauldron was inspired by Ancient God Tu Si's furnace.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.